Rikky Agung Nugraha

Front-end Web Developer

Komplek Borobudur, Candi Mendut III Street, G-3, No. 23, East Bekasi, 17111.

Summary

A Front-end Developer who has experience in building and maintaining responsive websites. Passionate about usability, reusable components, and problem-solving. React JS is one of the Front-end stuff that he could do. Committed to integrating the code in accordance with the expectations that are applied to the design.

Experience

Front-end Engineer - Internship

Sagara Technology (Jun 2022 - Sep 2022)

- · Took design ideas and transformed them into a successful web page.
- Website Development for application with Quasar Framework.
- · Integrated into RESTful API to make the application dynamic.

Document Control - Contract

PT. Surveyor Indonesia (Aug 2021- Dec 2021)

• Administration, and responsible for filling out the document

Front-end Developer - Internship

PT. Jasamarga (Persero) Tbk (Mar 2019 - Aug 2019)

- Designing a website from a wireframe
- Website development for application with Laravel Framework and styling using Bootstrap Framework.
- Develop a proper website for different devices

Education

Bootcamp React JS - Web Front-end Development

Sanbercode (Feb 2022 - Mar 2022)

Bachelor of Computer Science

STT Sapta Taruna (Sep 2014 - Nov 2020)

Major of Computer and Network Engineering

SMK Karya Guna 2 (Jul 2011 - May 2014)

Language

- Bahasa Indonesia
- English (Pre Intermediate)

Skill

- HTML
- SASS/SCSS

- Bootstrap
- Javascript (Beginner) Tailwind CSS
- React JS (Beginner)

Contact

<u>082213361558</u>

rikkyagung11@gmail.com

linkedin.com/rikkyagung

github.com/rikkyagung

rikkyagung.github.io

Hobby

- Playing Futsal
- Playing Guitar
- Traveling